<idea-plugin version="2">
  <id>com.paperetto.dash</id>
  <name>Dash</name>
  <version>3.1 beta 2</version>
  <vendor url="https://github.com/gdelmas/IntelliJDashPlugin">Gerard Delmàs</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
A simple and intelligent plugin for the IntelliJ Platform (IntelliJ IDEA, RubyMine, WebStorm, PhpStorm, PyCharm, Android Studio) that provides keyboard shortcut access for Dash.
<br />
<br />
<a href="http://flattr.com/thing/2558535/gdelmasIntelliJDashPlugin-on-GitHub" target="_blank"><img src="http://api.flattr.com/button/flattr-badge-large.png" alt="Flattr this" title="Flattr this" border="0" /></a>
<br />
<h3>Usage</h3>
The default shortcut assigned in the plugin is <b>Mac-Shift-D</b>.
It either uses the caret position for the search, or the current selection. The plugin will identify the currently used programming language through context and request filtered search results accordingly.
<br />
<h3>Dash</h3>
Dash is a Mac application for rapid search of developer documentation. There is a free, fully functional version with nags. It can be downloaded <a href="http://kapeli.com/dash">here</a>.<br />
<br />
<h3>What's new</h3>
In the past months I have been adding and testing new features for the plugin. I am now happy to release a lot of these additions that will make your search results just better. <br />
<br />
From now on code in strings will be detected. This way it is no longer necessary to select a specific word, the plugin will automatically know what you want to look up by the caret position. A lot of strings contain SQL code and for these your results will only from a SQL docset. In Project Settings -> SQL Dialects you can set which SQL docset you want to search. There are docsets available for MySQL, PostgreSQL and SQLite.<br />
<br />
If you have the "Regular Expressions" cheatsheet installed in Dash you can lookup groups, quantifiers and special characters really quickly. Just try and check what /\v/ means.<br />
<br />
Android projects get results from the Android docs, not Java. Java results depend on the projects SDK setting, searching either Java 6, 7 or 8. The same goes for Python 2 or 3. Apart from that I added support for Bash, Go, Haskell, Lua, Markdown, Scala and TypoScript. Language support for JavaScript and others has been extended.<br />
<br />
Simplicity is really important to me, that's why I always try to keep the plugin smart and settings free. I hope this help you spend less time searching the reference. Make the best of it.<br />
]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
<pre>
3.1
    - language detection support in strings
    - project settings sql dialect will be used
      to filter search results
    - android project support
    - java search results according to projects
      sdk version
    - python search results according to
      projects sdk version
    - added language support for: Bash, Go,
      Haskell, Lua, Markdown, Scala, TypoScript
    - extended language support for: angularjs,
      momen, require, awsjs, jasmine, sinon,
      tornado, sqlalchemy, numpy, scipy, salt,
      polymerdart, angulardart
    - performance and stability improvements
3.0.1 Fixed missing Ruby context recognition
3.0   Added Context aware search
2.2   Compatibility and stability fixes
2.1   Added Ruby syntax support, stability fixes
2.0   Added Dash docset keyword support
</pre>
]]>
  </change-notes>

  <!-- please see http://confluence.jetbrains.net/display/IDEADEV/Build+Number+Ranges for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="123.72"/>

  <!-- please see http://confluence.jetbrains.net/display/IDEADEV/Plugin+Compatibility+with+IntelliJ+Platform+Products
       on how to target different products -->
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
  <depends optional="true">com.intellij.sql</depends>

  <application-components>
    <!-- Add your application components here -->
  </application-components>

  <project-components>
    <!-- Add your project components here -->
  </project-components>

  <actions>
    <!-- Add your actions here -->
      <action id="DashLauncherAction" class="de.dreamlab.dash.DashLauncherAction" text="Search in Dash" description="Searches word under caret in Dash">
          <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="last"/>
          <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="ctrl shift D"/>
      </action>
  </actions>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <!-- Add your extensions here -->
  </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
